{
    "subject": "Vera_Nabokov",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Vladimir_Nabokov",
    "human_readable": "Vera Nabokov is married to Vladimir Nabokov.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9807135462760925,
            "question": "Are Vera and Vladimir Nabokov known to be married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9771785736083984,
            "question": "Name the person married to Vladimir Nabokov."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9674798846244812,
            "question": "Who is married to Vladimir Nabokov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9654045701026917,
            "question": "To whom was Vladimir Nabokov married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9238181710243225,
            "question": "What is Vera Nabokov's relationship to Vladimir Nabokov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8883170485496521,
            "question": "Is Vera Nabokov related to Vladimir Nabokov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8378540277481079,
            "question": "What is the name of Vladimir Nabokov's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8259783387184143,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the relationship between Vera and Vladimir Nabokov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7988972663879395,
            "question": "Who is Vera Nabokov?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7852205634117126,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Vera and Vladimir Nabokov?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Vera Nabokov is married to Vladimir Nabokov.",
            "html": "yago_30992_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Vera Nabokov?",
            "html": "yago_30992_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about the relationship between Vera and Vladimir Nabokov?",
            "html": "yago_30992_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Vladimir Nabokov's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_30992_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30992_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30992_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30992_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30992_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30992_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30992_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30992_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30992_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30992_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30992_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Vera Nabokov is married to Vladimir Nabokov. The documents mention their marriage in Berlin in 1925 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_30992/re-ranker-msmarco/65.txt), and describe V\u00e9ra as his wife, editor, and translator (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_30992/re-ranker-msmarco/80.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly indicate that V\u00e9ra Nabokov was the wife of Vladimir Nabokov, thus supporting the statement that Vera Nabokov is married to Vladimir Nabokov."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}